My mother's prescription
is really complicated.
I finally gathered all the ingredients.
Oh no,
not again.
We can talk
about this!
Help!
Stay
away!
No!
Actor Xia Yimo
You're awake.
Take it easy.
Be careful.
How do you feel?
How did I get here?
Where are you going?
Your wounds have not healed yet.
Where are you going, Ying'er?
Ning Yuanci!
How are you?
Are you hurt?
Let me see.
I am fine.
It is my fault.
I did not apply medicine to your wound.
My mother's healing salve
is very effective.
I will go get it for you now.
I... you...
You're Xue Keying,
right?
Or are you
Xia
Mo?
You...
You know everything.
What are you doing?
Ying'er is awake.
I need to go back and save her.
If you don't want Xue Keying
to be in danger again,
let me finish.
I know
you've always been harsh and cruel to me,
but I believe
you truly care about Xue Keying.
If you really want what's best for her,
when you go back.
don't say a word
to Xue Shiyan
Who would believe your nonsense?
Who knows what you and Ning Yuanci
are plotting
against my Ying'er?
Let me tell you,
the master loves Ying'er the most.
I'm going back right now to tell him
that you hid
Ying'er.
Just you wait.
Xue Shiyan doesn't love anyone.
He only cares about himself.
He could sacrifice my mother's life
and my marriage.
Do you think
Xue Keying would be an exception?
I seem
to have entered your dream.
That was a strange place.
And
I saw you
die in front of me
over and over again.
I also saw someone
who looked exactly like Xue Ruowan.
She called you Xia Yimo.
Can you tell me
what exactly is going on?
It's
a bit complicated.
It's hard for me to explain.
It's all Xuyu's fault
for making the plot so complicated.
Xue Keying,
you caused this mess,
yet you blame it on me.
Who is it?
Ning Yuanci can hear it too.
He can hear it
if I want him to.
Damn Xuyu.
I did everything you said,
but Xue Ruowan still got hurt.
You're just a big liar.
You pretend to obey,
but deep down you've been resisting
and fighting back.
The change in your character setting
affected the will of other characters,
causing the original plot to misalign.
That's what almost led to
an irreversible ending.
Keying,
what's going on?
And you even dragged Ning Yuanci
into this.
Making us swap bodies,
how could you come up with that?
There was no body-swapping plot
in the Mo Xiang script.
It's a small loophole created
when I asked the writer to fix
the main storyline.
However,
I saw you and Ning Yuanci
bound by fate
and connected in mind
at the moment of life and death.
It's quite interesting.
Interesting.
Are the lives of characters
not lives?
We almost died.
You gave Ning Yuanci
awareness and emotions beyond the script.
How will you complete
the plot missions next
and reach the grand finale of the story?
I'm really looking forward to it.
Good luck,
Xue Keying.
Is this my last
chance?
Say something.
It's getting late.
I-I have to go back
and fool Xue Shiyan.
I'll explain it to you later.
Don't go.
I really have to go.
Otherwise Xue Shiyan will get suspicious.
You're not going anywhere
until you explain it to me today.
If I say
I don't belong to this world,
and this world isn't
what you think it is,
would you believe me?
I believe you.
I don't care where you're from.
What I care about is
whether the person in front of me
has ever
truly liked me.
You said you liked me before,
but it was all fake,
right?
No.
That's not right.
I was acting,
but...
What am I saying?
Okay.
I know.
You don't understand.
I really do like you.
You can't fake true feelings.
You should be able to feel that.
You asked me
if I was Xue Keying.
I am her,
but not entirely.
I don't even know
how to explain it to you.
What you just said
is enough.
As for the plot
and tasks
the system mentioned,
they don't matter.
The important thing is
I know
you like me.
Xue Keying,
Xue Ruowan,
What's wrong?
Even though
I know
it's too late,
I still want to say I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have acted on my own.
I almost got you killed.
There's no need to keep score between us.
Actually,
I've remembered a lot
about our childhood lately.
Our childhood?
Sister, play with me.
Sister,
play with me.
Come here.
I've held a grudge against you
since we were little.
But I forgot
that I was the one who coldly
pushed you away first.
Because I was jealous
of the love you got from our parents,
I treated you
as an enemy.
Later, when you opened your heart to me,
I thought
you were just pitying me.
Sometimes I longed to be
a truly good sister to you,
but other times,
I wished
you were just a bad person.
That way, I would be the only one
getting hurt.
Growing up,
I haven't been a good sister.
Can you forgive me?
When we get famous later,
we can become
international superstars.
Then we'll act in the same show.
and go down in cinematic history.
Then who plays the lead
and who plays the supporting role?
We'll be co-leads.
Co-leads?
As if we'd ever
be that lucky.
Just because it hasn't happened yet
doesn't mean it won't.
As long as we work hard,
we will definitely succeed.
Actually, I'm at fault too.
I often acted self-righteous,
thinking it was for your own good,
but I ignored your feelings.
Even knowing that things
weren't what I thought,
I still picked fights with you
and refused to clear things up.
I wanted to get closer,
but I used the worst possible way.
I...
From now on,
just stay where you are.
Let me be the one to come to you.
Don't worry.
No matter how many times we start over,
I will never give up on saving you.
But right now,
I must earn
Xue Shiyan's trust.
I might
have to become the person you hate again.
Putting on an act...
isn't that
what you're best at, silly girl?
As long as I know
who you truly are, that's enough.